<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="VisualVM_Launcher"
      label="VisualVM_Launcher Feature"
      version="1.0.1"
      provider-name="Sun Microsystems">

   <description>
      VisualVM is a visual tool integrating several commandline JDK
tools and lightweight profiling capabilities. Designed for both
production and development time use, it further enhances the
capability of monitoring and performance analysis for the Java
SE platform.
This launcher makes monitoring your eclipse based applications
as easy as launching them from the IDE.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.example.com/copyright">
      Copyright (c) 2007, 2011, Oracle and/or its affiliates. All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.gnu.org/software/classpath/license.html">
/*
* Copyright (c) 2007, 2011, Oracle and/or its affiliates. All rights reserved.
* DO NOT ALTER OR REMOVE COPYRIGHT NOTICES OR THIS FILE HEADER.
*
* This code is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it
* under the terms of the GNU General Public License version 2 only, as
* published by the Free Software Foundation.  Oracle designates this
* particular file as subject to the &quot;Classpath&quot; exception as provided
* by Oracle in the LICENSE file that accompanied this code.
*
* This code is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT
* ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or
* FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU General Public License
* version 2 for more details (a copy is included in the LICENSE file that
* accompanied this code).
*
* You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License version
* 2 along with this work; if not, write to the Free Software Foundation,
* Inc., 51 Franklin St, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA 02110-1301 USA.
*
* Please contact Oracle, 500 Oracle Parkway, Redwood Shores, CA 94065 USA
* or visit www.oracle.com if you need additional information or have any
* questions.
*/
   </license>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="com.ibm.icu"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.launching"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.visualvm.launcher.common" version="1.0.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.pde.ui"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.visualvm.launcher.common"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.visualvm.launcher.java"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.eclipse.visualvm.launcher.pde"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

</feature>
